[Music]
hi oh I had something in my
teeth welcome to the show where we
examine impossible questions with
science analysis and some DOA that's
amazze balls tonight we examine what if
high fives never
existed what is the greeting of a
generation were to suddenly be wiped
out I'll get that hey professor bitching
party last night
thanks that might happen good job here
at the unfocused group some ex students
of mine are experimenting with some
potential high five
Replacements let's
see uh a bit
exotic that is a high five keep
[Music]
trying uh that's fine but I've got an
idea how about
this huh how about that I think this is
a potential breakthrough what are you
guys doing it's the new high
five but the true laboratory to show how
the high five would be replaced is on
the streets of America where people walk
the streets and do Street things if we
couldn't do a high five what would we
do
I waited for my boner to die and then I
had heard a rumor that high five started
in sports so I met a pro athlete in a
car with coffees Jay Jay I'm over here
and I brought coffee thanks man you want
this one I'll go with a bigger cup I
ain't got all
day so who invented the high five yeah I
think it was Dusty Baker and Burke right
all right now get
out that's it thank you thanks Jay
thanks appreciate
it shut the door thank you so what if
Dusty and his teammates or anyone else
for that matter hadn't develop this
celebratory
salutation uh have you ever heard of the
butterfly effect that is if there was no
high-fiving maybe there would be no
computers there's always going to be
computers yeah because cuz we have
high-fiving yes oh I was just posting up
for a high
five yes nice one but without high fives
How will I know someone's my best friend
I mean you guys could just be friends
you could do stuff together and you
could know each other for a long time
you're so naive let's just get
high and not talk
anymore students whilst taking
my daily afternoon stroll all of a
sudden it dawned on me I needed to speak
to Dusty Baker himself his name Dusty
Baker my sources told me that you
invented the high five I really don't
know you know I think it was Glenn Berke
on my teammate talk us through it how it
happened you were on the baseball field
I was on the baseball field laying with
the Dodgers and I hit it over center
field fence Glen Burke was a young
teammate at the time mhm and then next
thing I know he put his hand up so he
put his hand up up yeah he put it way
back up like this you go I don't know
what to do yeah I knew what to do just
to hit it would it be okay if we
reenacted that magical high five that's
cool now let me see how hip you are cuz
see Glenn was real hip I wear an earring
sometimes no that's that's that's pretty
hi Glenn he's call me Johnny B and so
Glenn was he reached way back here like
this oh and he's like Johnny B Johnny
B yeah that's how it is wow so say that
never happened what would replace that
some of these guys are like they'll go
like give me give me the other hand like
this and then boom
boom that's it that's too much oh that's
too much to do and it's too much to
remember and that's what happened when I
met my best friend Rusty Baker wasn't it
Dusty Baker uh well I mean he's Rusty
like he hasn't played in a while did he
give you an answer about a replacement
for a high five
um well uh answers that's so vague
speaking of answers what if high fives
never existed the world would adopt the
Estonian folk tradition of arm cradling
good night everybody let's try it huh
everybody up there we go huh see
no hey
touchdown
yeah bowling
strike hey hey Cricket
smash isn't it I think it's going to
replace it let's start doing it every
day